A Guide to the Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
The Library of Virginia
24666, 25914, 26467, 26618, 26801, 27025, 27211, 27428, 27605, 27789, 28095, 28344, 28748, 29239, 29633, 30058, 30803, 30942, 31163, 41004
366 boxes, 165 cubic feet
State Corporation Commission
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by Virginia State Corporation Commission, 28 August 1957 (24666), 10 September 1963 (25914), 1 March 1966 (26467), 6 January 1967 (26618), 24 October 1967 (26801), 13 September 1968 (27025), 5 August 1969 (27211), 11 August 1970 (27428), 28 July 1971 (27605), 2 August 1972 (27789), 10 September 1973 (28905), 12 August 1974 (28344), 22 August 1975 (28748), 10 September 1976 (29239), 11 October 1977 (29633), 28 September 1978 (30058), 26 October 1979 (30803), 14 November 1980 (30942), 29 August 1981 (31163), no acquisition information (41004)
Biographical/Historical Information
The State Corporation Commission was created by the state constitution adopted in 1902, to replace the Board of Public Works. It is independent of the executive, legislative, and judicial branches of government, but holds many of their powers, including the authority to issue and revoke corporation charters, to set the rates to be charged by public utilities, and generally to regulate the activities of corporations conducting business in Virginia. An independent Department of Corporations was created by the General Assembly on April 18, 1927, and the Commission was placed within it. The Commission is made up of three members elected by joint vote of both Houses of the General Assembly. The chairman is elected by the members. Specific purpose, powers and duties are: charter and supervise domestic corporations and license foreign corporations; further regulate rates, charges, and services of railroads, telephone, gas and electric companies. Regulatory duties extend to aviation, telegraph, water and sewer companies, to those banks, savings and loan associations, industrial loan associations, credit unions and small loan associations, industrial loan associations, credit unions and small loan companies which it licenses; supervise and license insurance companies and enforce motor carrier laws; collect State's gross receipts, road taxes and motor fuel road taxes, and assess for local taxation real and personal property of all public service companies; and administer laws governing securities and retail franchising. The Commission has an administrative office and a legal office to support the regulatory divisions, which are: Bureau of Financial Institutions, Bureau of Insurance, Motor Carrier Division, Public Service Taxation, Public Utilities, Railroad Regulation Division, and Securities and Retail Financing.
Scope and Content
These annual operating reports for railroads consist of bound volumes for individual railroad companies. Reports include information on the following: company history and organization, officers, property, stock, debt, income and earnings, expenses, contracts, employees and salaries, equipment, accidents, taxes, and assessments.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into one series:
Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads
This collection is arranged chronologically and thereunder alphabetically by the name of the railroad with a few exceptions.
Contents List
- Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975., Extent: 366 boxes; 165 cubic feet. (Box 1-366)
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1899.
    - Farmville and Powhatan, 1899 (Box 1)
  - 1900.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Big Stone Gap, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Danville and Western, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Farmville and Powhatan, 1900 (Box 1)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1900 (Box 1)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Potomac, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Rockbridge, Alum, and Goshen, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1900 (Box 2)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Seaboard and Roanoke, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Southern, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Southern Railroad Company Operations of Atlantic and Danville, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Southern Railway Company Operation of Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Suffolk and Carolina, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Sulphur Mine, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Tuckahoe and James River, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Valley, 1900 (Box 3)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1900 (Box 4)
    - Washington and Southern, 1900 (Box 4)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1900 (Box 4)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1900 (Box 4)
  - 1901.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1901 (Box 4)
    - Big Stone Gap, 1901 (Box 4)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1901 (Box 4)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1901 (Box 4)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1901 (Box 4)
    - Cumberland and Martinsburg, 1901 (Box 4)
    - Danville and Western, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Farmville and Powhatan, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Gladeville, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Louisville and Nashville, Cumberland Valley Division, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Marion and Rye, 1901 (Box 5)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Potomac, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1901 (Box 5)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Rockbridge, Alum, and Goshen, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Southern, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Southern Railway Company Operation of Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Suffolk and Carolina, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1901 (Box 6)
    - Tuckahoe and James, 1901 (Box 7)
    - Valley Railroad, 1901 (Box 7)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1901 (Box 7)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1901 (Box 7)
    - Washington and Southern, 1901 (Box 7)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1901 (Box 7)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1901 (Box 7)
  - 1902.
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1902 (Box 7)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1902 (Box 7)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1902 (Box 7)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Cumberland Valley and Mecklenburg, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Danville and Western, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Farmville and Powhatan, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Louisville and Nashville, Cumberland Valley Division, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1902 (Box 8)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1902 (Box 8)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Potomac, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Rockbridge, Alum, and Goshen, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Southern, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Southern Railway Operation of Atlantic and Danville, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Southern Railway Operation of Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Southern Railway Operations of Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1902 (Box 9)
    - Southern and Carolina, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Tuckahoe and James River, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Valley, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Washington and Southern, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1902 (Box 10)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1902 (Box 10)
  - 1903.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Danville and Western, 1903 (Box 11)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virgina (2 folders), 1903 (Box 11)
    - Farmville and Powhatan, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Interstate, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Lick Creek and Lake Erie, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1903 (Box 12)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1903 (Box 12)
    - Potomac, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Rockbridge, Alum, and Goshen, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Southern, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Southern Railway Operation of Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1903 (Box 13)
    - Southern Railway Operation of Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Suffolk and Carolina, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Valley, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Washington Southern, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1903 (Box 14)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1903 (Box 14)
  - 1904.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1904 (Box 15)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1904 (Box 15)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1904 (Box 15)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1904 (Box 15)
    - Big Stony (2 folders), 1904 (Box 15)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1904 (Box 15)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1904 (Box 15)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1904 (Box 15)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Danville and Western, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Farmville and Powhatan, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Interstate, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Lick Creek and Lake Erie, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1904 (Box 16)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1904 (Box 16)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1904 (Box 17)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Potomac, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1904 (Box 17)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1904 (Box 18)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1904 (Box 18)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1904 (Box 18)
    - Southern Railway, 1904 (Box 18)
    - Suffolk and Carolina, 1904 (Box 18)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1904 (Box 18)
    - Valley, 1904 (Box 18)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1904 (Box 19)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1904 (Box 19)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal and Railway, 1904 (Box 19)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1904 (Box 19)
    - Washington Southern, 1904 (Box 19)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1904 (Box 19)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1904 (Box 19)
    - Wise Terminal, 1904 (Box 19)
  - 1905.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1905 (Box 19)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1905 (Box 19)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Big Stony, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Danville and Western, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Delaware, Maryland and Virginia, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Farmville and Powhatan, 1905 (Box 20)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1905 (Box 21)
    - Indian Creek and Powell River, 1905 (Box 21)
    - Interstate, 1905 (Box 21)
    - Lick Creek and Lake Erie, 1905 (Box 21)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1905 (Box 21)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1905 (Box 21)
    - Mount Airy Eastern, 1905 (Box 21)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1905 (Box 21)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1905 (Box 21)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Potomac, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1905 (Box 22)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Southern, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Suffolk and Carolina, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Valley, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal and Railway, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Washington and Southern, 1905 (Box 24)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1905 (Box 24)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1905 (Box 24)
    - Wise Terminal, 1905 (Box 24)
  - 1906.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1906 (Box 24)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1906 (Box 24)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1906 (Box 24)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1906 (Box 24)
    - Big Stony, 1906 (Box 24)
    - Black Mountain, 1906 (Box 25)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1906 (Box 25)
    - Chesapeake and Western (2 folders), 1906 (Box 25)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1906 (Box 25)
    - Danville and Western, 1906 (Box 25)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1906 (Box 25)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1906 (Box 25)
    - Indian Creek and Pound River, 1906 (Box 25)
    - Interstate, 1906 (Box 26)
    - Lick Creek and Lake Erie, 1906 (Box 26)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1906 (Box 26)
    - Marion and Rye, 1906 (Box 26)
    - Mount Airy Eastern, 1906 (Box 26)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1906 (Box 26)
    - New River, Holston, and Western 1906 (Box 26)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1906 (Box 26)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1906 (Box 26)
    - Norfolk and Southern (2 folders), 1906 (Box 27)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Potomac, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg and Piedmont, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1906 (Box 27)
    - Southern, 1906 (Box 28)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1906 (Box 28)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1906 (Box 28)
    - Valley, 1906 (Box 28)
    - Virginia and Carolina Coast (2 folders), 1906 (Box 28)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1906 (Box 28)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1906 (Box 28)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal and Railway, 1906 (Box 28)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1906 (Box 29)
    - Virginia Southern, 1906 (Box 29)
    - Washington Southern, 1906 (Box 29)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1906 (Box 29)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1906 (Box 29)
    - Wise Terminal, 1906 (Box 29)
  - 1907.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1907 (Box 29)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1907 (Box 29)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1907 (Box 29)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Big Stony, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Black Mountaint, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Blackstone and Lunenburg, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Danville and Western, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1907 (Box 30)
    - Elizabeth River, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Indian Creek and Pound River, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Interstate, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Lick Creek and Lake Erie, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Mount Airy Eastern, 1907 (Box 31)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1907 (Box 31)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1907 (Box 31)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Pocahontas and Western, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Potomac, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1907 (Box 32)
    - Roaring Fork, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1907 (Box 33)
    - South and Western, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Southern, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Valley, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Virginia, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1907 (Box 33)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Virginia - Carolina and Southern, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Southern, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Washington Southern, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1907 (Box 34)
    - Wise Terminal, 1907 (Box 34)
  - 1908.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1908 (Box 34)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Big Stony, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Black Mountain, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Blackstone and Lunenburg, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Danville and Western, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Delware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Elizabeth River, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1908 (Box 36)
    - Interstate, 1908 (Box 37)
    - Laurel, 1908 (Box 37)
    - Lick Creek and Erie, 1908 (Box 37)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1908 (Box 37)
    - Lynchburg Belt Line and Connecting, 1908 (Box 37)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1908 (Box 37)
    - Mount Airy Eastern, 1908 (Box 37)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1908 (Box 38)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1908 (Box 38)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1908 (Box 38)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1908 (Box 38)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1908 (Box 38)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1908 (Box 38)
    - Pocahontas and Western, 1908 (Box 38)
    - Potomac, 1908 (Box 38)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1908 (Box 39)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1908 (Box 39)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1908 (Box 39)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1908 (Box 39)
    - Roaring Fork, 1908 (Box 39)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1908 (Box 39)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1908 (Box 39)
    - South and Western, 1908 (Box 39)
    - Southern, 1908 (Box 40)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1908 (Box 40)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1908 (Box 40)
    - Valley, 1908 (Box 40)
    - Virginia Air Line, 1908 (Box 40)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1908 (Box 40)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1908 (Box 40)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal, 1908 (Box 41)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1908 (Box 41)
    - Virginia Southern, 1908 (Box 41)
    - Washington Southern, 1908 (Box 41)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1908 (Box 41)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1908 (Box 41)
    - Wise Terminal, 1908 (Box 41)
  - 1909.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1909 (Box 41)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Big Stony, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Blackstone and Lunenburg, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1909 (Box 42)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Danville and Western, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Elizabeth River, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Interstate, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Laurel, 1909 (Box 43)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1909 (Box 44)
    - Lynchburg Belt Line and Connecting, 1909 (Box 44)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1909 (Box 44)
    - Mount Airy Eastern, 1909 (Box 44)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1909 (Box 44)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1909 (Box 44)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1909 (Box 44)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1909 (Box 44)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Pocahontas and Western, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Potomac, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Richmond and Petersburg, 1909 (Box 45)
    - Roaring Fork, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Southern, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Valley, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Virginia, 1909 (Box 46)
    - Virginia Air Line, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Virginia Southern, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Washington Southern, 1909 (Box 47)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1909 (Box 48)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1909 (Box 48)
    - Wise Terminal, 1909 (Box 48)
  - 1910.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1910 (Box 48)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1910 (Box 48)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland 1910 (Box 48)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1910 (Box 48)
    - Big Stony, 1910 (Box 48)
    - Big Stony, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Blackstone and Lunenburg, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Bluestone, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1910 (Box 49)
    - Citizens Railway Light and Power Company, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Danville and Western, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Danville Railways and Electric Company, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Delware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Great Falls and Old Dominion, 1910 (Box 50)